atlasandboots.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy | Atlas & Boots

## Our privacy policy

We want visitors to our website to be able to take part fully in the activities and offers we provide. We also want to make sure that when we collect information from you, we do so in a way that does not infringe your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to give you useful information about the way we collect and use personal information and how we use cookies.

By using our website you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Personal information

We will not collect any personal data from you unless you specifically provide it and we will only use that information for the purposes to which you have consented. We do not ask you to provide any more information than is reasonably necessary to enable you to participate in an activity on our website and to improve the website.

We do not generally disclose your personal information to third parties. We may have to sometimes, in which case we will inform you of our intention to do so when we collect the information and you will have the opportunity to consent to that use or not.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not maintain any personal information obtained from users through this website in a retrievable form.

**The information that we collect and how we use it**

Below are some examples of when we might request your information and how we will use it.

**Newsletter**

We have a weekly roundup that keep readers up-to-date with our latest posts. If you would like to subscribe, we will require your email address so that we can send the newsletter to you. We may also ask you to provide other information about yourself, such as your name, age, sex and location so that we can personalise your newsletter.

**Prize promotions**

We occasionally run competitions and prize draws and, in addition to your answer or entry, we will require you to send us certain information, such as your name and email address. We will only use this information to administer the promotion and for any other purpose to which you consented when you entered.

**Email and other contact details**

You may wish to contact us from time to time by sending us letters or emails. We will only use this information to respond to your query or suggestion.

**Cookies**

We use cookies on this site to enable certain parts of the site to function and to collect non-personal information about your use of the site so that we can improve our visitors’ experience.

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device by websites that you visit. They cannot harm your computer and do not contain any information that enable us to identify you personally, they just enable our websites to recognise your computer and to identify certain other non-personal information such as which browser you are using. This information can be used to make the website work, to identify which parts of the site can work better or to analyse how often people visit the site and what they look at. We will not associate this data with any personally identifying information that you may choose to provide to us in other ways.

By your using this website, we imply that you have read this policy and agree to us sending you cookies.

## Affiliates

Please note that some of the links on our website are affiliate links. This means that at no additional cost to you, we will earn a commission if you decide to make a purchase after clicking the link. We use all of these companies and recommend them because they are helpful and useful, not because of the small commission we earn.

## How to contact us

If you have any questions about this website or our privacy policy, please contact us by writing to [contact@atlasandboots.com](mailto:contact@atlasandboots.com).

_First posted: 10 March 2015_
